Don't die on me, Aki.
So that when I die...
You can cry for me.
Snake: Swallow it whole.
Leave.
The Fiend ran off.
We're after Chainsaw's heart.
Don't bother with her.
This time, I'm gonna split him in two.
Don't damage the heart.
I dunno what the fuck's going on...
But it's easy enough to tell
you two are bad guys.
I love bad guys, y'know...
Nobody gives me any shit
when I carve 'em up!
So I get to kill you a second time.
Die!
This is Sawatari.
We've engaged Chainsaw on the third
floor of the Nerima Nishidai building.
Send reinforcements.
Yeow!
Do we shoot?
Aim for the arms or the heart.
Asshole!
Ow, ow, ow...
Huh. When'd he even cut me?
Ow!
Hey, bad guy!
He's one of your buddies, right?
What's your point?
I dare you to move a millimeter!
Or I'll turn your buddy-boy's
head into ground beef!
Asshole.
Yeah, that's right! Sit your ass down!
Where'd he go?
Let's move him. Get the car, now.
Hurry it up.
All of Chainsaw's people should be dead.
I guess Devil Hunters are still human...
Meaning they can't win against guns.
Guns...
We're almost at the station.
Let's move through the cars
and split up among the civvies.
Tendo!
Special Divisions 1 through 4 all came
under assault in Tokyo.
Seriously? Is Ms. Makima dead?
Ugh. Have we been wasting our time here?
Wha...
Kurose. Tendo.
There was a shooting on the train.
The bodies are still there,
so take care of them.
The lunch meeting is canceled.
There were shots fired in Tokyo, too.
Ms. Makima, you're covered in blood!
Were you hit?!
This isn't mine.
I wasn't shot.
Things are in chaos over there,
so we don't have a lot
of reliable information.
They're apparently still
confirming the casualties.
So... should we head to Tokyo
as backup right now?
We won't make it in time if we do.
The enemy is probably after Denji.
I'll do what I can from here.
Kurose, I need you to borrow 30 convicts
with life sentences or worse
from the Ministry of Justice.
Tendo, find the nearest temple with
the highest altitude, and reserve it.
Also...
I need some clean clothes, if you would.
Where are we going?
Hell if I know.
Hey, no talking back there.
Ms. Makima...
They're almost here.
Thank you, Tendo.
I'll be right there.
Move it.
I'm gonna be out of action for a bit.
Mm.
So heavy... Gimme a hand here!
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Hold him up on that end.
How exactly is this supposed to work?
Hey!
Hey, come on already!
Something's... what the hell?
Quit freaking out! Just lift.
I'm telling you, something's weird!
What exactly do you mean by...
Team E, have Team C verify Makima's body.
This is Team E. Team E here.
Team C hasn't been in contact since...
That bitch.
Why exactly are we blindfolded?
Ms. Makima reports directly
to the Chief Cabinet Secretary.
Rank-and-file Devil Hunters like us don't have
clearance to know about her devil contracts.
Say the name "Shuzo Mishima."
Shuzo Mishima...
We need to get Chainsaw moving, now!
G-Got it!
Hey! Into the car!
Damn it! Are you listening to me?!
Mishima!
Say the name "Takashi Inoue."
Takashi Inoue...
Hey!
No!
Somebody help!
It's over.
You can take those off.
That's all that can be done from here.
I need to get back to Tokyo.
A bullshit power like this
is bound to be Makima.
Let's get out of here while we still can.
Damn it! I thought they killed her.
You two...
are with the shooters, aren't you?
Snake.
Tail!
What is she, a monkey?!
Shit!
You can die in the van!
I'm sorry I tried to kill you the other day.
Apologizing for attempted murder...
What the heck?
This is bad... I'm freaking out!
He protected me.
It's my... my fault...
I... I'm just...
I can't do this... This job
is going to drive me nuts!
I'll have to tell Himeno
I'm quitting when I see her again.
I'm glad to see you alive, Madoka.
How much of the Special Divisions survived?
Special Divisions 1, 2, 3, and 4
all came under assault,
and just about everyone is dead
except for the non-humans.
An assault with guns,
targeting the Special Divisions...
It seems like the Gun Devil
must be involved.
I've got a message from up above.
Due to the personnel shortage, Divisions 1,
2, and 3 will be absorbed into 4.
And as of now, Public Safety Devil
Extermination Special Division 4
will be under your command, Makima.
Also, this.
What is it?
My resignation.
You're quitting?
The Special Division seems
like bad news at this point.
I figure the choice is between
quitting or getting killed.
I see.
There's one last thing I'm curious about.
How much of what happened today
did you anticipate, Ms. Makima?
I'm afraid I can't share Public
Safety intel with private citizens.
Thank you for your service, Madoka.
I'll pass this along.
Uh... Ms. Makima,
you know we're not actually joining
your Special Division, right?
We're just here to help with training, okay?
And in a week, we'll be
heading right back to Kyoto.
That's a shame.
The dining in Tokyo is to die for.